

Dilara Pirkishiyeva

Young professional with a broad history of work experience in Geographical Research, Tourism Industry, and Journalism. Dependable and organized team player with a wide range of skills and the ability to communicate effectively and efficiently.

in

+994 70 213 08 98

dilara.pirkishieva@gmail.com

Dilara Pirkishiyeva



Azerbaijan, Sumgait. AZ 5000

Work Experience



Private Company. USA, West Palm Beach, FL.

Research Manager. October 2018 - July 2020

- Gather geographic data through observations, maps, photographs, satellite imagery, and censuses which were submitted by amateurs and professionals.
- Link geographic data with data pertaining to a particular specialty, such as economics, the environment, health, or politics.
- Conduct research via surveys, interviews, and focus groups

Turizm.az Group of Companies. Baku, Azerbaijan

Processing Manager February 2019 - July 2019

- · Email data extraction of potential customers.
- · Handling cash & bank related transactions if assigned.
- Maintaining & recording all application data in a timely and accurate manner.
- Investigate the integrity of documents and other information in connection with visa applications.
- · Provide high levels of client service. Liaise with clients, organizations, other visa offices, other agencies within the Embassy and relevant agencies within the host country and Azerbaijan.

"Zaman və Biz" Newspaper. Baku, Azerbaijan

Special Correspondent August 2019 - Current

- · Report and write news stories for publication or broadcast, describing the background and details of events.
- · Arrange interviews with people who can provide information about a particular story.
- Review copy and correct errors in content, grammar, and punctuation, following prescribed editorial style and formatting guidelines.
- · Review and evaluate notes taken about event aspects in order to isolate pertinent facts and details.
- · Determine a story's emphasis, length, and format, and organize material accordingly.

EU Neighbors EAST. European Union

Young European Ambassador September 2018 - Current

- · Represent the youth of our country and network with young people from the European Union and the Eastern partner countries.
- Exchange ideas, knowledge and experiences, discuss matters of concern to young people, share best practices, and work together for a better future.
- · Visit universities and schools to spread awareness about first world problems.
- Brainstorming ideas and participating in training and workshops.

Educational History

BAKU STATE UNIVERSITY

Bachelor's Degree 2015 - 2019 Geography

Skills Summary

- Platforms: Microsoft Windows XP, Vista, Windows 7 & 8, MAC OS.
- Hardware & Networking: Windows & Android based devices Desktops, Laptops, printers, DSL Modem, Routers.
- Tools: Active Directory MS Office Suite (Excel, Word, PowerPoint, FrontPage and Access), Outlook, Fox mail and other Email Client Software configuration, Blogger.

- Positive attitute with grounded optimism
- Exceptional communication skills, highly organized, collaborative and detail oriented
- Excellent problem solving, time management and organizational skills
- Assessing and prioritizing multiple tasks, projects and demands
- Establishing and maintaining effective working relationships with co-workers and the public.
- Ability to interact, communicate and negotiate effectively
- Measure and observe customer usage and satisfaction and incorporate those findings into product and service developments
- Skills in multicultural work environment
- Additional set of hard/soft skills appreciated by employers

Languages



- Azerbaijani Native
- English Proficient
- Russian Mother tongue
- Turkish Mother tongue
- Ukrainian Pre-intermediate.

Additional information

- Campbell University & DHS Foundation Awardee of 2020 for being The Best Social Worker
- Sustainable Development Changemaker in Habiba Community Egypt
- Volunteer work in organizations as AARC, USEIC, Wildlife Sense Greece
- Representative of Anex Tour in Azerbaijan International Tourism Fair